ILGWU. Publications 5780 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Justice: ILGWU 60th Anniversary Issue Vol.XLII, No.11-12, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Business Week Magazine: May 9th, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Business Week: June 16, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Time Magazine Vol.LIV, No.9, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Live… (Box 28, Folder 18)
- $100 Million in "Rags", 1963 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- American Labor Magazine, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Protocol of Peace, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Commentary: August Vol.8, No.2, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- The Schooling of David Dubinsky, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Safeguarding Union Welfare Funds: Should Labor Support Legislation?, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Union Education for Leisure, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Life Magazine: December 12, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Newsweek Magazine: October 15, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- D.D. (Box 29, Folder 1)
- The New Republic Vol.154, No.14, Issue 2680, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Life Magazine Special Issue: The Good Life (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Labour News Summer 1966 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- The New York Times Magazine December 12, 1949, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- How the Politburo Thinks and Letter to a Confused Liberal, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Monthly Labor Review Vol.73, No.5, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Today Magazine Vol.VII, No.1, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Ramparts Vol.8, No.4, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Time Magazine Vol.LXVII, No.1, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Life Magazine Vol.39, No.24, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Life Magazine Vol.25, No.4, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- A Policy Guide on Enforcing the Union Agreement (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Life Magazine Vol.12, No.5, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- The New Leader Vol.XLIII, No.31, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- This is a Union Shop: You and the ILGWU (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Committee Meeting: August 26, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- A Warning Against Communists in Unions, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Machinists Monthly Journal: September, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Working Union: You and the ILGWU (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Constitution and By-Laws of the ILGWU, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Know Your Union Benefits (Box 29, Folder 22)
- A Guide for Cloakmakers in the Greater New York Area Concerning Retirement Benefits, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- 35 Northeast, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- McCall's Magazine Vol.XCVII, No.3, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- New York Sunday News: April 20, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Why Wait?, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- The Bobbin Magazine Vol.1, Issue 4, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Say It With Pictures, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- 50 Golden Years. Waterproof Garment Workers' Union, Local 29, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Labor Chronicle Vol.60, No.10, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Every Worker Should Be Earning at Least $1.25 an Hour (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Your Best Friend Will Tell You! (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Re: Union Label, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Travel in Style: A Handbook of Travel and Vacation Wardrobes, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- 1944 at Stake in 1942: A Trade Unionist Looks at the New York State Election (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Life International Magazine Vol.25, No.4, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Life Magazine Vol.39, No.24, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Liberty Magazine. July 1950. "What Liberty Means to Me" (Box 30, Folder 15)
- The New Leader Vol. XLIX, No.8, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Labour News from the United States, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Giants of Justice (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Report of the Education Department: June1951-May 1953 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- The New Leader Vol.XLIII, No.31, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- The Rise of David Dubinsky, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- ILGWU: The Old Age of a Union, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- 1942 and 1944 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Structure and Functioning of the ILGWU, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Labour and World Affairs Vol.XI, No.6, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- 37 Years Young! 1910-1947 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Coming of Age Celebration, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Report of the Committee on National and International Relations (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Workers' Education- CIO Model, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Convention Festival Concert, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- The ILGWU: Useful Facts about the ILGWU (Box 31, Folder 8)
- La ILGWU: Datos Utiles Para Los Miembros de La International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Our Union Vol.11, No.4, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Local 23-25 News (Box 31, Folder 11)
  Chinese and English.
- Why We Don't Want the Scab Council (Box 31, Folder 12)
- The Dress Industry Report No.19, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Ninth Annual Music and Drama Festival, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Save Life and Liberty with the ILGWU Women's Health Brigade, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- ILGWU and Histadrut (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Presented to the 26th Convention, ILGWU (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Scholastic: The American High School Weekly Vol.38, No.11, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Northeast Report: 1947 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Greetings Delegates. ILGWU 40th Anniversary Convention, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Publications 1939 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- ILGWU Publications 1942-1943 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Women in the American Labor Movement (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Pressers 35 Jubilee, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Coming-of-Age Celebration, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- The ILGWU Speaks: What Next?, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- An Outline of the Problems Involved in This Strike. A Guide to Speakers Prepared by the Speakers' Committee., 1930 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- A Union Accepts Youth's Challenge, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Workers' Education-CIO Model, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- The Emancipator, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Outline of Lecture "Mental Delousing Stations", 1939 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Tom Mooney: Victory After 22 Years, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Liberty Vol.15, No.35, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Workers' Education 1900-1940 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Gerechtigkeit (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Sasha, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- The Workmen's Circle Call Vol.36, No.5, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- The American Federationist, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  v.74:no.5 (1967)
- Trends and Prospects in the Women's Garment Industry 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Why New York Needs the Beame Team (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Un Team Granador Para Nueva York! (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Social Action: The NLRB Why and How Vol. IV, No.9, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Twelve Good Reasons for Joining a Union (Box 32, Folder 19)
- In the Beginning: Children's Dress, Infants' Wear, Housedress and Bathrobe Makers Union (Box 32, Folder 20)
- The Truth about the ILGWU (Box 32, Folder 21)
- What is May Day and Why We Celebrate It (Box 32, Folder 22)
- An Outline of the Background, Character and Activities of the Country-Wide Organization of the Coat and Suit Field (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Lincoln's Birthday Dinner under the Auspices of the New York City Central Labor Council, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Trends and Prospects in the Women's Garment Industry 1962-1965 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- The American Federationist, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  v.80:no.3 (1973)
- Dressmakers: All About Your Benefits (Box 32, Folder 27)
- To the Delegates…ILGWU Golden Jubilee Convention, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- The ILGWU Story, Our Union and Civil Rights, Our Union and Politics and Facts About Local 23 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- How A Major Labor Union, ILGWU, Uses Historical Perspective to Arouse Social Concern, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Journey Into ILGWU History, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Weekly Compilation of Presidential Documents Vol.4, No.22, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Welcome! (Box 32, Folder 33)
  Spanish. 2 copies.
- Welcome! (Box 32, Folder 33)
  Chinese.
- Education is a Must (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Sing-A-Long with the ILGWU (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Letter to Fellow Guidesmen, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- 30 Yoriger Yubileaum (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Journey Into ILGWU History (Box 32, Folder 38)
- The Message Vol.II, No.29 (Box 32.1, Folder 1)
- Crerand's Cloak Journal Vol.XXXVIII, No.3A (Box 32.1, Folder 2)
- Union Benefit Program (Box 32.1, Folder 3)
- En La Union Esta La Fuerza (Box 32.1, Folder 4)
  Spanish. 5 copies.
- Financial Report 1963 General Funds (Box 32.1, Folder 5)
- Financial Report 1965 General Funds (Box 32.1, Folder 5)
- Financial Report and General Funds (Box 32.1, Folder 5)
- Financial Report and General Funds (Box 32.1, Folder 5)
- Financial Report and General Funds, 1971 (Box 32.1, Folder 5)
- Financial Report and General Funds (Box 32.1, Folder 5)
- Financial Report 1962 General Funds (Box 32.1, Folder 5)
- Our Aim Vol.VII, No.61-Vol.Vol.VIII, No.75, 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Our Aim Vol.IX, No.76-Vol.X, No.95, 1945-1947 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Our Aim Vol.III, No.16, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Redaction Vol.1, No.1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Redaction Vol.1, No.2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- El Organizador Vol.1, No.1, 1934 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- S.T.E.P. Vol.1, No.6-Vol.5,No.1, 1970-1974 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Conditions in the Women's Garment Industry, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Technology and Labor in the Post War Era, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- 1972 ILGWU Benefit Funds (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Consumer Education and Labor, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Welcome to Local 62 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- To Plan the Future No.1 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- A Trade Unionist Looks at Job Evaluation, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Recognition of a Staff Union of Business Agents Under the National Labor Relations Act, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- 1979 Financial Reports and General Funds (Box 33, Folder 13)
- A Contribution to America's Victory and to Italy's Freedom: First Annual Report of the Italian-American Labor Council, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- New Frontiers for Labor (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Program of the Dressmakers Progressive Group, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Higher Education and Organized Labor, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- The Struggle for Schools, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Training of Apparel Workers and Subsidies, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Step by Step…1941-1966 A Report of 25 Years of Progress (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Gerechtigkeit Vol.XXIX, No. 6, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- The Voice of the Needle, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- International Free Trade Union News Vol.2, No.3, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Thirty-Hour Week Classified Wages Bi-Party Codes, 1935 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- The Reviewing Stand Vol.5, No.17, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Worth Dreaming…, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- "Red" Unions and the AFL, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- The Communists and the Unions, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- The Workmen's Call Vol.41, No.3, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- American Labor and Racial Equality (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Handling of Union Welfare Funds, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Conference to Combat Intolerance, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- A Tribute to the Retirees of the ILGWU, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Multinationals: A Global Menace (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Labor's Multinational Pains, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Der Bruder-Krig in Di Idishe Yunions (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Motivating the Worker, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Examples of Headlines and Sub-Headlines Taken From the Freiheit, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Sexism and the Unions, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Labor in the 1980s: A New Challenge, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Out of the Sweatshop: Commemorating the 75th Anniversary of the ILGWU, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Technology 1971, Vol.5: Changes in the Garment Industry (Box 34, Folder 10)
- The New Leader Vol.LVIII, No.13, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- The New Leader Vol.LV, No.12, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- The New Leader Vol.LV, No.23, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- The Challenge of Change and Conflict in American Society, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Souvenir Program, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Garment Workers Speak (Box 34, Folder 16)
- The Needle Worker Vol.II, No.5, 1926 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- The Ladies' Garment Worker in History and Shop, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Organized Labor and Politics as a Factor in the 1936 Election (Box 34, Folder 19)
- A Kampfs-Program For Di Dresmakher (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Di Ryote Nodl (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Machinists Monthly Journal Vol.XLIII, No.7, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Organized Labor's Contribution to the Nation (Box 34, Folder 23)
- New York: Our City, Our Union. 24th Convention of the ILGWU, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Workers' Education in the United States, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Left and Right in the Needle-Trades Unions, 1924 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- In Memoriam: Dr. Aron Syngalowski (Box 35, Folder 1)
- American Journal of Public Health and the Nation's Health Vol.38, No.7. Some Labor Union Enterprises in Public Health Economics (Box 35, Folder 2)
- 60th Anniversary 1912-1973 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- History in the Making, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Twenty-One Years of Health Education Among Wage-Earners, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Machinists Monthly Journal Vol.XLIV, No.8, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- The Short, Unsung Life of a Tailors Union of the 1860s, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Education: Why and For What, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Workers and the Arts, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- What Should Schools Teach About Unionism? Harvard Educational Review, Vol.12, No.4, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Closed Minds are Dead Minds, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Planning for Freedom, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Seventh Avenue-Road to Improved Labor-Management Relations, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Labor and Education (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Management and Labor Make Strong Medicine, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Some Current Myths About Labor, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Labor Defends America, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- New Dangers for the Needle Trades, 1923 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Labor Looks Forward- The Call, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Industrial Bulletin, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- The Government and the Worker (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Our First Fifty Years (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Labor Dialogue: Africa-U.S., 1978 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Pictorial Union Dictionary, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Digest: Federal Social Security and State Unemployment Insurance Laws, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Where to Go in New York, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- ILGWU Suggestions for Social, Educational and Recreational Programs for Our Local Unions, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- The Drive to Improve the Federal Minimum Wage Law, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Your Money's Worth, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- What the Citizen Should Know About Labor, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- In the Needle Trades: Moves Towards Closer Union, Step by Step (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Teachers Clear Decks for Action, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- Born of Change: A Union Meets the Challenge Posed by New Buying Habits, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- Work Analysis of the Board of Control for Enforcement of Protocol Standards in the Waist and Dress Industry, 1916 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- Labor and the American Way, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Industry's Responsibility for Worker Health- American Journal of Public Health and the Nation's Health Vol.39, No.3, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Fascists and Fascist Deeds (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Health and Welfare Funds in the Needle Trades- Industrial and Labor Relations Review Vol.1, No.2, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Labor and the Nation Vol.III, No.3, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Municipal Campaign Rally, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Joint Board Cloakmakers' Union of New York Thirty-Fifth Anniversary Jubilee Book 1910-1945 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Moved to Oversized "G" (Box 36, Folder 8)
- The Tresca Case (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Our Aim: Local 91 Gives Relief to Members in Need Vol.I, No.6, 1935 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Industrial Bulletin Vol.26, No.3, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Report of the Pacific Coast International Locals, 1934 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- The Home of 91 Official Opening, 1943 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Italo-American Friendship- Pillar of World Peace and Democracy, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Souvenir Journal, 1923 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Report of Activities of the Association, 1918 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Gateway Heritage Vol.2, No.1, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Local 91 Introduces "The American Way" (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Let Them March in Their Rags (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Fashion for the Millions: The Sewing Machine in America, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Bertha The Sewing Machine Girl (Box 36.1, Folder 1)
- How "Pins and Needles" Was Born (Box 36.1, Folder 1)
- Cast- "Pins and Needles"-Road Company (Box 36.1, Folder 1)
- Social Significance (Box 36.1, Folder 1)
- Pins and Needles (Box 36.1, Folder 1)
- Pins and Needs Music and Lyrics, 1937 (Box 36.1, Folder 2)
- Pins and Needles, 1938 (Box 36.1, Folder 2)
- How "Pins and Needles" Was Born (Box 36.1, Folder 2)
- The Joint Board of Sanitary Control: A Brief Review of One of the First Attempts at Industrial Self-Control in the Women's Garment Industry, 1930 (Box 36.1, Folder 3)
- Seventeen-at-School Vol.19, No.6, 1965 (Box 36.1, Folder 4)
- Life Magazine, 1946 (Box 36.1, Folder 5)
- Five Who Led, 1976 (Box 36.1, Folder 6)
- US Court of Appeals: ILGWU against NLRB Brief of Petitioner ILGWU, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- How We Tell Our Story, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Dress Shipping Clerks: A Member of the ILGWU Family, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Labor Stuff: Project for a Local 22 Union School Magazine, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- The Needle's Eye: 100 years of Machine Sewing, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Meyer London, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Publicity Guide (Box 37, Folder 7)
- The Chinatown Garment Industry Study, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Souvenir Journal Golden Jubilee: 50 Years of Progress, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Barikht Fun Der Laydis Wayst Un Dresmakher Yunion Lokal 25 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- The Dressmakers' Union Must Again Become the Pride of the Labor Movement (Box 37, Folder 11)
  English, Italian and Yiddish. 2 copies.
- We Are the ILGWU (Box 37, Folder 12)
- The Union Health Center of the ILGWU (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Workers' Education in the ILGWU 1937-1940: Excerpts from General Executive Board Report to the ILGWU Convention (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Industrial Bulletin No.33, No.12, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Political Activity and the Law (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Dia Konvenshen Moskito (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Busy Dubinsky Cloak and Suiters Make Their Union a Big Business, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- This is Your Union…This is the ILGWU (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Brother…Can You Spare a Finger? (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Testimonial to John S. Martin, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Our Secret Weapon, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Souvenir Journal to Establish Old Age Fund, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Good News No.103, 1937 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Good News No.104, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Good News No.107 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- The Jewish Labor Movement: A Living Legacy (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Apparel Industry Chapter Honors David Dubinsky (Box 38, Folder 12)
- 70th Birthday Reception Tendered to Frank R. Crosswaith by the Negro Labor Committee, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Report of the Ohio-Kentucky Region, ILGWU 28th National Convention, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Testimonial Tendered by Italian Cloakmakers Union, Local 48, ILGWU to Edward Molisani, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Freedom Award Dinner in Honor of David Dubinsky, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Partners Vol.I, No.1, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- 50th Anniversary Gala Concert 1916-1966 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- ILGers Pinpoint Life and Labor in Sri Lanka, India, South Africa, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Through the Needle's Eye: A Book of Readings (Box 38.1, Folder 1)
- Through the Needle's Eye: A Book of Readings (Box 38.1, Folder 2)
- Through the Needle's Eye: Part II (Box 38.1, Folder 3)
- Through the Needle's Eye: A Book of Readings (Box 38.1, Folder 3)
- Why Union Education? Aims, History, Philosophy of the Educational Work of the ILGWU, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Labor and the Public (Box 39, Folder 2)
- The Journal of the Institute of Socioeconomic Studies Vol.VIII, No.2, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- The Cloakmaker's Strike of 1910, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- The Journal of Social Issues Vol.IX, No.2, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Wages and Regularity of Employment and Standardization of Piece Rates in the Dress and Waist Industry: New York City, 1914 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Free Labour World No.108, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Three Cents an Hour: An Intimate Picture of Industrial Home Work in Pennsylvania, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- A Statement from the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, 1916 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- In Memoriam: Victor Alter Henryk Erlich- The Living Record of Two Leaders of Labor, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- To Honor John S. Martin for 46 Years of Service to the American Labor Movement, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Industrial Ophthalmology, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- The Northeast Department's 30th Anniversary, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Watch Out for the Wolf!, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Local 22 Art Workshop Exhibition, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Health Program of ILGWU, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Trabajador de la Aguja esta Tu Union (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Calendar: Golden Jubilee Convention, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- ILGWU Cooperative Village: A Dream Come True (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Twentieth Anniversary Reunion of the 1910 Cloakmakers General Strike Committee, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  English and Yiddish. 3 copies.
- Unser Tshit (Box 39, Folder 21)
- International Labour Review Vol.LVIII, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Der Wecker Vol.LXI (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Der Wecker Vol.V, No.272, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Steel, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  25 copies.
- Our World Vol.4, No.2, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- The Big Strike of 1910, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- We Urge, We Urge, We Urge (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Sixty Years of Fashion: 1900-1960, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Voice of the Knitgoods Workers Vol.1, No.1, 1934 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- 20th Anniversary Celebration Luncheon Entertainment and Dance, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Ten Years of Industrial Sanitary Self Control in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt and Dress and Waist Industries of New York, 1921 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- WSR Newsletter Vol.1, No.1 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- WSR Newsletter Vol.1, No.2, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- WSR Newsletter Vol.1, No.3, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- WSR Newsletter Vol.1, No.4, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- WSR Newsletter Vol.1, No.5, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- WSR Newsletter Vol.1, No.6, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- WSR Newsletter Vol.1, No.7, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- WSR Newsletter Vol.1, No.7, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  Chinese. 3 copies.
- Bertha the Sewing Machine Girl (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Dixie Dress-Maker Seasons Greetings (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Facts About Dues (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Underwear Union News- Spring 1940 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The Dixie Dressmaker, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The Dixie Dressmaker, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The Dixie Dressmaker, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The Dixie Dressmaker, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The Dixie Dressmaker- Convention Issue, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Thanks a Million (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Facts About the Wage-Hour Law (Box 40, Folder 7)
- A Private Word with Alternation Workers, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Small Town Shop Problems Answered (Box 40, Folder 7)
- An Answer to the Newspaper Attack Against a Union for the Workers at the E.Z. Mills in Cartersville, Georgia (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The Dixie Dressmaker- June 1939 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The Dixie Dressmaker- July 1939 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The Dixie Dressmaker-November 1939 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Signal Mills News, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Underwear News, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Underwear Union News-May 1940 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The Signal Light-May 1942 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- A Saturday Night Problem, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Life Vol.5, No.5, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Celebrating 75 Years of Service 1914-1989 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Calendar: 40th Anniversary Convention, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Let the Record Speak, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 11)